capitalbank-us.com 2019-10-23

# Privacy Notice for Customers of the First Horizon Family of Companies

## Facts

What does the First Horizon Family of Companies do with your personal information?

First Tennessee Bank National Association, operating as First Tennessee Bank and Capital Bank, is part of the First Horizon family of companies.

### Why?

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.

### What?

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include: 

  * Social Security number and income
  * Payment history and account balances
  * Credit score and credit history

### How?

All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons the First Horizon family of companies chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.

Reasons we can share your personal information | Does the First Horizon family of companies share? | Can you limit this sharing?  
---|---|---  
For our everyday business purposes, such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus | Yes | No  
For our marketing purposes – to offer our products and services to you | Yes | No  
For joint marketing with other financial companies | Yes | No  
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes – information about your transactions and experiences | Yes | No  
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness | Yes | Yes  
For our affiliates to market to you | Yes | Yes  
For non-affiliates to market to you | Yes | Yes  
  
### To limit our sharing

Call [877-242-9880](tel:8772429880) – our menu will prompt you through your choice(s)

Please note:  
If you are a _new customer_ , we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are _no longer_ our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.

However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.

### Once I limit sharing, what if I change my mind?

If you have opted out of sharing, but you have changed your mind and would like to authorize us to share your information for permissible purposes (including to non-affiliates for marketing purposes), you may opt in by submitting a written request. Download an easy form to complete and give us permission to begin sharing your information for marketing and other permissible purposes.

Once you download the form, please complete it and mail your Opt-In Authorization request to: Account Services/Account Records Dept. - FOPW, 3451 Prescott, Memphis, TN 38118 for processing. Due to state privacy laws, the Opt-In form is not for use with residents of California, Illinois, North Dakota, or Vermont.

### Questions?

Use one of the following three options:

  * Call [877-242-9880](tel:877-242-9880).
  * Send a message by logging into Digital Banking.
  * Send a message by visiting www.ftb.com/questions or www.capitalbank-us.com/questions.

The Privacy Notice can be found online by visiting www.ftb.com/privacy or www.capitalbank-us.com/privacy.

### Who we are?

**Who is providing this notice?**   
Financial institutions within the First Horizon family of companies that provide lending, investment, and insurance products and services. First Tennessee Bank National Association, operating as First Tennessee Bank and Capital Bank, is part of the First Horizon family of companies.

### What we do

**How does the First Horizon family of companies protect my personal information?**  
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.

**How does the First Horizon family of companies collect my personal information?**  
We collect your personal information, for example, when you

  * Open an account or apply for a loan
  * Use your credit or debit card or apply for insurance
  * Seek advice about your investments

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.

**Why can't I limit all sharing?**  
Federal law gives you the right to limit only

  * Sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
  * Affiliates from using your information to market to you
  * Sharing for non-affiliates to market to you

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.

**What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?**  
Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.

### Definitions

**Affiliates**  
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.

  * _Our affiliates include companies with a First Horizon/First Tennessee name; financial companies such as First Tennessee Bank; and others such as FTB Advisors Insurance Services, Inc._

**Non-affiliates**  
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.

**Joint marketing**  
A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.

  * _Our joint marketing partners include insurance and investment companies._

### Other Important Information

For California Residents: We will not share personal information with affiliates or non-affiliates except as necessary for us to follow the law or as permitted by law.

For Vermont Residents: We will not disclose information about your creditworthiness to our affiliates, and will not disclose your personal information, financial information, credit report or health information to non-affiliated third parties to market to you other than as permitted by Vermont law. We may provide your name, contact information and transaction information to companies that perform marketing services for us or financial institutions with which we have joint marketing arrangements.

For Illinois and North Dakota Residents: We do not share your personal information for joint marketing with other financial institutions. We do not share your personal information with non-affiliates to market their products or services to you.

For Insurance (Including Annuity) Customers: We do not share information we collect related to any insurance transaction with us with non-affiliates to market to you. Residents of certain states may receive additional information concerning use and sharing of information we collect related to an insurance transaction with us.

For Nevada Residents: In accordance with Nevada law, you may request to be placed on the internal do not call list for the First Horizon Family of Companies. To be placed on this list please call [877-242-9880](tel:877-242-9880).

Online Privacy Notice: The Online Privacy Notice for the First Horizon Family of Companies is available at www.ftb.com and www.capitalbank-us.com. The Online Privacy Notice describes how we use and collect information about our website users.

### The First Horizon Family of Companies:

Capital Bank*  
First Horizon*  
First Horizon Bank*  
First Horizon Equity Lending*  
First Horizon Home Loans*  
First Horizon Insurance Services, Inc.  
First Tennessee Bank National Association  
FTB Advisors, Inc.  
FTB Advisors Insurance Services, Inc  
First Tennessee Home Loans*  
FTN Financial Capital Markets*  
FTN Financial Main Street Advisors, LLC  
FTN Financial Securities Corp.
